<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>52</title>
    <link>http://10.0.0.66:5011/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 52</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="http://10.0.0.66:5011/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Double Lift</title>
      <link>http://10.0.0.66:5011/library/sleight/double-lift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://10.0.0.66:5011/library/sleight/double-lift/</guid>
      <description>The double lift is a move used to appear to show the first (top) card, when actually you are showing the second card.
Get a thumb break underneath the second card (so, two cards on top of it). Push the cards together is such a way as to make it look like you have only one card, using any grip you wish. Lift up the top two cards as one, making sure to have control over every edge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Lift Reveal</title>
      <link>http://10.0.0.66:5011/library/reveals/double-lift-reveal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://10.0.0.66:5011/library/reveals/double-lift-reveal/</guid>
      <description>An amazing sleight of hand ending for if the card is on top! (made by Toby!)
Make sure the card is at the top (if you are nervous, do a riffle to check) and prepare for a double lift. Do a double lift and show the face (of the second card). Say, &amp;ldquo;This is not your card, correct?&amp;rdquo; The spectator shall agree with you. Place the two cards back on top and then put the top card (their card) on the table, saying, &amp;ldquo;so we shall place it on the table&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Library</title>
      <link>http://10.0.0.66:5011/library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://10.0.0.66:5011/library/</guid>
      <description>A library of Magic
Reveals Double Lift Reveal Shuffles and Cuts Overhand Shuffle Sleight of Hand Double Lift </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overhand Shuffle</title>
      <link>http://10.0.0.66:5011/library/shuffle-cut/overhand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://10.0.0.66:5011/library/shuffle-cut/overhand/</guid>
      <description>The easiest, most versitile shuffle. Also great to
Get into Shuffle Grip. Cut off roughly the bottom 2/3 of the deck and lift them up. Come down, drop a few cards (a packet) then move back up. Repeat step 3 until all the cards are back in your left hand. Repeat steps 2-4 until you are satisfid. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
